A Guide to the Joseph B. Benedetti Papers 1983-1997
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series Two 1986-1997
  - Fictitious Transportation Costs 1987 (Box 58)
  - Finance-Budget Amendments 1997 (Box 58)
  - Fire-History Museum (SB 60) 1990 (Box 58)
  - First Offender Failed (SB 405) 1990 (Box 58)
  - First Offender Program (SB 772) 1991 (Box 58)
  - Fish Ladder (HB 981) 1989 (Box 58)
  - Fish Passage notes 1988 (Box 58)
  - Forced or Assisted Suicide 1995 (Box 58)
  - Forfeiture of Vehicles 1992 (Box 58)
  - Forrest Lands 1984 (Box 58)
  - Four Year Term (SB 9) 1994 (Box 58)
  - Free use of Toll Facilities (SB 775) 1989 (Box 58)
  - Games or Lotteries (SB 19) 1996 (Box 58)
  - Garbage Pick-up and Disposal 1987 (Box 58)
  - Garnishment and Unemployment 1987 (Box 58)
  - Governor Allen Budget and State of the Commonwealth Address 1996 (Box 58)
  - Governor's School 1994 (Box 58)
  - Greater Richmond Regionalism study 1996-1997 (Box 58)
  - Grievance Procedures (SB 467) 1996 (Box 58)
  - Health Care Plan Key Advantage 1992 (Box 58)
  - Historic Preservation (SB 514) 1992 (Box 58)
  - HIV Testing-Prostitutes (SB 354) 1992 (Box 58)
  - HMO-Medicaid 1995 (Box 58)
  - Homeless 1994 (Box 58)
  - Housing Redevelopment 1988 (Box 58)
  - Hunting Small Game (SB 304) 1996 (Box 58)
  - Immobile Vehicle (SB 353) 1988 (Box 58)
  - Immunity for Local Volunteers 1997 (Box 58)
  - Independent Sales Representatives (SB 706) 1993 (Box 58)
  - Individual Income Tax (SB 403) 1990 (Box 58)
  - Information Techinical Courts (SB 1021) 1995 (Box 58)
  - Instant Bingo 1992 (Box 58)
  - Invitations 1984-1985 (Box 58)
  - IOLTA 1994 (Box 58)
  - Issues-Joe's Districts 1996-1997 (Box 58)
  - JBB No Votes 1997 (Box 58)
  - John Tyler Community College 1995 (Box 58)
  - Joint Custody 1986 (Box 58)
  - Joint Felony Trials 1997 (Box 58)
  - Joseph B. Benedetti 1992 (Box 58)
  - Judges 1994 (Box 58)
  - Judgeship Nominees 1992 (Box 58)
  - Judicial Authorization of treatment (SB 355) 1992 (Box 58)
  - Jury Trials (SB 158) 1990 (Box 58)
  - Juvenile Assaults (SB 20) 1997 (Box 58)
  - Juvenile Crime and Justice 1986 (Box 58)
  - Juvenile Crime and Justice 1986 (Box 59)
  - Juvenile Fingerprints (HB 450) 1986 (Box 59)
  - Juvenile Judgeships (SR 20) 1990 (Box 59)
  - Juvenile Justice Reform 1996 (Box 59)
  - Juvenile Victims and Witnesses 1994 (Box 59)
  - Landlord and Tenant Act 1987-1991 (Box 59)
  - Landowner/Railroad Proposal 1994 (Box 59)
  - Lease of Pelham Chapel (SB 707) 1993 (Box 59)
  - Legislation-bills not filed 1996 (Box 59)
  - Legislation Introduced 1994 (Box 59)
  - Legislative Agenda 1983-1989 (Box 59)
  - Legislative Directory 1996 (Box 59)
  - Legislative Impact Statement 1986 (Box 59)
  - License Tax on illegal Substances 1991 (Box 59)
  - Licensure of Marriage and Family Therapists 1993 (Box 59)
  - Licensure of Radiological Technologists 1994 (Box 59)
  - Licensure of Substance Abuse Counselors 1997 (Box 59)
  - Limitation of Authority for BPOL taxes 1994 (Box 59)
  - Loca License Tax 1990 (Box 59)
  - Local Mandates 1995 (Box 59)
  - Loitering Ordinances in Drug Area (SB 298) 1994 (Box 59)
  - Loitering for Prostitution 1993 (Box 59)
  - Lottery Fund; Enhancing 1995 (Box 59)
  - Lottery Prizes Garnishment 1995 (Box 59)
  - Marriage and Family Therapists (SB 473) 1994-1995 (Box 59)
  - Mary Sue 1991 (Box 59)
  - Mayor at Large (HB 231) 1996 (Box 59)
  - Mayor-Term of Office (SB 415) 1987 (Box 58)
  - MCV-Funding 1995 (Box 59)
  - Medicaid Fraud; actions to recover 1996 (Box 59)
  - Medical Assistance Service 1996 (Box 59)
  - Medical Records as Evidence (SB 281) 1992 (Box 59)
  - Medical Society of Va 1988 (Box 59)
  - Memorial Resolutions 1987-1991 (Box 59)
  - Minority Business Loan 1995 (Box 59)
  - Motel/Hotel Rehabilitation (SB 822) 1993 (Box 59)
  - Motor Vehicle Emission Reduction Program 1996 (Box 59)
  - Motor Vehicle Insurance (SB 555) 1996 (Box 59)
  - Motor Vehicle Sales and Use Tax (SB 960) 1993 (Box 59)
  - Motor Vehicle Scrappage (SB 820) 1993 (Box 59)
  - Multi-Purpose Enhanced Records Check (SB 972) 1993 (Box 59)
  - Music Licensing Fees (SB 858) 1995 (Box 59)
  - Neighbors for Benedetti 1992 (Box 59)
  - News Columns 1992-1994 (Box 59)
  - Newsletters 1993 (Box 59)
  - No Votes 1990-1991 (Box 59)
  - Nutrition 1994 (Box 59)
  - Notice of Issuance of Warrants (SB 879) 1993 (Box 59)
  - Occupational Safety and Health (SB 1036) 1997 (Box 60)
  - Ordinances Prohibiting Alcohol in Public Parks 1994 (Box 60)
  - Ordinances Prohibiting Firearms in Public Parks 1994 (Box 60)
  - Parental Consent and abortion 1987 (Box 60)
  - Parole (SB 187) 1992 (Box 60)
  - People Helpers Foundation (SB 715) 1995 (Box 60)
  - Persons Receiving Lottery Prizes (SB 627) 1996 (Box 60)
  - Pleadings (SB 404) 1990 (Box 60)
  - Preferred Venue (SB 303) 1994 (Box 60)
  - Press-Release 1994 (Box 60)
  - Procurement Preference Va Vendors (SB 827) 1993 (Box 60)
  - Prof. Regulation: Substance abuse treatment 1997 (Box 60)
  - Property Tax Exemptions (SB 522) 1987-1988 (Box 60)
  - Records-Drugs 1991 (Box 60)
  - Redistricting (SB 771) 1991 (Box 60)
  - Regional Cooperation 1994 (Box 60)
  - Regional Transportation 1995 (Box 60)
  - Regulation of Garbage (SB 774) 1991 (Box 60)
  - Regulations Nursing Homes 1996 (Box 60)
  - Repeal of Personal Property Tax 1997 (Box 60)
  - Republican Position on General Issues 1996 (Box 60)
  - Request for Legislative Drafting 1990 (Box 60)
  - Residency Requirements 1993 (Box 60)
  - Residential Property Disclosure (SB 823) 1993 (Box 60)
  - Resolution Rehab. Services (SR 4) 1994 (Box 60)
  - Resolution on a Balanced Budget 1996 (Box 60)
  - Retail sales tax exemption charitable (SB 556) 1993 (Box 60)
  - Retirees Settlement (SB 2008) 1994 (Box 60)
  - Richmond Charter 1989-1996 (Box 60)
  - Richmond International Airport 1996 (Box 60)
  - Richmond Metro Authority 1992 (Box 60)
  - Richmond Regional Authority 1995 (Box 60)
  - Richmond Regional Cooperation 1994 (Box 60)
  - Richmond Speaks 1990 (Box 60)
  - Riverboat Gambling 1995 (Box 60)
  - Robert Kirkpatrick Memorial Resolution 1989 (Box 60)
  - Roll Call Votes 1992-1995 (Box 60)
  - Rules-Conflict of interest subcommittee 1992 (Box 60)
  - Salaries-General Assembly 1987 (Box 60)
  - Sales Tax Exemption 1997 (Box 60)
  - Saltwater Fishing License Fees 1994 (Box 60)
  - SCC Judges selection 1996 (Box 60)
  - Seizure and Forfeiture of Vehicles (SB 781) 1989 (Box 60)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth 1994 (Box 60)
  - Senator Benedetti Newspaper Articles 1992 (Box 60)
  - Senate Bill 15 Special Session 1986 (Box 60)
  - Senate Bill 5 1986 (Box 60)
  - Senate Budget Amendment 1996 (Box 60)
  - Senate Calendar 1997 (Box 60)
  - Senate Finance Subcommittee on Compensation 1997 (Box 61)
  - Senate Rules (SR 5) 1993-1994 (Box 61)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure 1995 (Box 61)
  - Service Districts 1987-1989 (Box 61)
  - Sexually Explicit Visual Materials 1989 (Box 61)
  - Statewide Fire Prevention 1989 (Box 61)
  - Shared Custody (307) 1994 (Box 61)
  - Siegal, Charles (HJR 169) 1986 (Box 61)
  - Slayer Act 1992 (Box 61)
  - Social Security Benefits 1992 (Box 61)
  - Special License Plate 1991-1995 (Box 61)
  - Special Service districts (SB 458) 1988 (Box 61)
  - Speeches 1994 (Box 61)
  - Speeches for Ozell 1996 (Box 61)
  - Standards of Learning 1995 (Box 61)
  - State Insurance Trust Fund 1996 (Box 61)
  - State Library Budget Amendment 1997 (Box 61)
  - State of the Commonwealth Address 1992 (Box 61)
  - Study Cost effective basic government (SJR 383) 1995 (Box 61)
  - Study Regulation of Bingo Games and Raffles (SJR 179) 1989 (Box 61)
  - Stuff from Visitors and Lobbyists 1997 (Box 61)
  - Summary Judgement 1995 (Box 61)
  - Survey of New Constituents 1991 (Box 61)
  - Survey of NO. VA voters 1992 (Box 61)
  - Tasting Licenses (SB 442) 1996 (Box 61)
  - Tax on Cannabis and controlled substances (SB 780) 1989 (Box 61)
  - Tax on Drugs 1994 (Box 61)
  - Tax Exemption (SB 533) 1991 (Box 61)
  - Tax on Illegal Drugs 1989-1990 (Box 61)
  - Telecommunications Bill (SB 1013) 1997 (Box 61)
  - Trafficking the Dead 1989 (Box 61)
  - Transfer of juveniles (SB 305) 1994 (Box 61)
  - Transient Occupancy Tax (SB 556) 1996 (Box 61)
  - Transportation Trust Fund (SB 671) 1987 (Box 61)
  - Unathorized Use of name (SB 771) 1995 (Box 61)
  - Unemployment Compensation for newspaper carriers 1997 (Box 61)
  - Urban Partnership 1996 (Box 61)
  - Urban System Highway (SB 459) 1989 (Box 61)
  - Vehicle Emissions Inspection (SB 961) 1993 (Box 61)
  - Veto Session 1995 (Box 61)
  - VA. Fish Passage Grant (SB 460) 1989 (Box 61)
  - VA. Health Spa Act (SB 283) 1992 (Box 61)
  - VA. Human Rights (SB 1025) 1995 (Box 62)
  - Virginia Municipal League 1995 (Box 62)
  - VMI/Mary Baldwin 1994 (Box 62)
  - Waiver of Liability (SB 1022) 1995 (Box 62)
  - Water Discharge Permits 1994 (Box 62)
  - Water Resources (SB 455) 1988 (Box 62)
  - Wetlands 1992 (Box 62)
  - Wheat Securities (SB 573) 1994 (Box 62)
  - Will and Estates (SB 909) 1997 (Box 62)
  - World Class System of Education 1992 (Box 62)
  - Zip Codes 1994 (Box 62)
  - Zoning Violations 1990 (Box 62)